<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<QuestionForm xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2005-10-01/QuestionForm.xsd">
	<Overview>
		<FormattedContent><![CDATA[
			<h1 align="center">Generate a schema</h1>
			<h1>Instructions</h1>
			<p>
				<b>
					Problems share patterns which describe the structure and essence of problems abstractly.
					In this task, we would like you to generate a pattern for a problem. We will first demonstrate
					the process of generating a pattern through an example.
					<font color="red"> Read the instruction carefully, otherwise you risk being rejected.</font>
				</b>
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>An example problem:</b>
				<i>In cold weather, you often find single dropped gloves lying on the street lonely.
				Almost everyone, not only kids, has lost one of their gloves, leaving the other useless. It is frustrating
				and a waste of money. How can we solve the problem of losing gloves?</i>
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>A similar problem:</b>
				<i>Women like wearing earrings. But they get lost very easily. There's nothing more frustrating than
				looking in the mirror and realizing you've lost an earring or going to grab a pair from your dresser and finding
				only one. How can we solve the problem of losing earrings?</i>
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>By comparing the gloves-dropping problem with the earrings dropping problem, we can generate a pattern for the gloves-dropping problem like this:</b>
				<i>Some objects need to work together in a pair. The problem is one of the pair is often lost leaving their partner useless. How can we prevent losing one of the pair?</i>
			</p>
			<p>
				The pattern describes the structure and essence of the problem without mentioning the specific domain information such as gloves. In this task, we would like you to generate a pattern for the following problem:
			</p>
			<p><i><font color="green">$problem</font></i></p>
			<p><b>We know this task can be challenging. Please follow the steps that can help you generate a good pattern.</b></p>
		]]></FormattedContent>
	</Overview>
	<Question>
	    <QuestionIdentifier>1</QuestionIdentifier>
	    <IsRequired>true</IsRequired>
	    <QuestionContent>
	        <Text>Step 1: Please describe the above problem in your own words: how do you describe it to a friend? Copy and paste is not allowed. </Text>
	    </QuestionContent>
	    <AnswerSpecification>
	        <FreeTextAnswer/>
	    </AnswerSpecification>
	</Question>
	<Question>
	    <QuestionIdentifier>2</QuestionIdentifier>
	    <IsRequired>true</IsRequired>
	    <QuestionContent>
	    	<Text>Step 2: Can you think of a similar problem in a different domain? </Text>
	    </QuestionContent>
	    <AnswerSpecification>
	    	<FreeTextAnswer/>
	    </AnswerSpecification>
	</Question>
	<Question>
		<QuestionIdentifier>3</QuestionIdentifier>
		<IsRequired>true</IsRequired>
		<QuestionContent>
		 	<Text>
		 		Step 3: Now please generate a pattern for the problem.
				Tip 1: You can map the objects between our problem and the one you came up with to generate the shared structure.
				Tip 2: The pattern should describe the characteristics of the objects in the problem and the relation structure between objects.
			</Text>
		</QuestionContent>
		<AnswerSpecification>
		    <FreeTextAnswer/>
		</AnswerSpecification>
	</Question>
</QuestionForm>
		  